<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Synical Approach</title>
    <link>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Synical Approach</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:55:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://SynfulChaot.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SEO (for the Lazy)</title>
      <link>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/seo-for-the-lazy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/seo-for-the-lazy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As of the writing of this post, it is quite difficult to find this blog &amp;hellip; and by &amp;lsquo;difficult&amp;rsquo; I mean you&amp;rsquo;re not gonna find it without the URL or a link.  &lt;em&gt;Obviously&lt;/em&gt; I want a bit more than that if I&amp;rsquo;m writing a blog.  After all, if I only wanted to share all of this with my closest friends then I could already do that via Discord and the like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to the rescue!  Time to add in those annoying but somewhat crucial details that the brainless robots used by search engines need to actually grok what a website is and what it contains.  Maybe in time they&amp;rsquo;ll be smart enough, but we&amp;rsquo;re &lt;em&gt;nowhere&lt;/em&gt; near that point just yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Hugo</title>
      <link>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/customizing-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 02:40:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/customizing-hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I knew going in that the theme I had chosen, &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/vaga/hugo-theme-m10c&#34;&gt;m10c&lt;/a&gt;, was pretty barebones.  I went with it, still, because it was clean, lightweight, no JS whatsoever, and had &lt;em&gt;a&lt;/em&gt; sidebar.  That being said, I also knew going in that I was going to mod the heck out of this thing to get to where I wanted it to be.  I suppose I just wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting to need to start at that &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But.  If I want to get people&amp;rsquo;s attention, if I want to get an audience, then I &lt;em&gt;definitely&lt;/em&gt; needed something a &lt;em&gt;&lt;del&gt;bit&lt;/del&gt; lot&lt;/em&gt; more than the default.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I think I &lt;em&gt;&lt;del&gt;found&lt;/del&gt; made&lt;/em&gt; it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Discourse</title>
      <link>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/enabling-discourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 21:22:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/enabling-discourse/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now back when I was first considering this blog, a good few years ago, I had no intention of comments.  It was purely going to be a place for me to dump my ideas and thoughts and all that.  Nothing less.  Nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I got to thinking about it, though, I realized that, despite the risks that are inherent in opening yourself up to the feedback of random Intarweb strangers, the benefits outweigh the risks.  I mean &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; some people are &lt;em&gt;absolutely awful&lt;/em&gt; examples of our species, but at the same time it can be helpful to hear what others think about your content.  Perhaps people might want more details, or sometimes less, or are curious about other things that you may usually cover.  Perhaps someone will correct you, in which case not only you, but also your readers, get to learn new things.  Perhaps they want to point you towards things that are related or that they think you might be interested in.  Or, perhaps, people just want to thank you for your content.  Whatever the reason, comments can be a real boon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, lets be honest, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have comments where you &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; see them, if enough people are reading your blog then it&amp;rsquo;s likely that they&amp;rsquo;ll start up some comments where you &lt;em&gt;can&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; &amp;hellip; or at least where you don&amp;rsquo;t know where they are, but the difference there really is trivial if you think about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So without further ado!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginning the Journey</title>
      <link>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/beginning-the-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://SynfulChaot.github.io/posts/beginning-the-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So it has been an age and a day since I last entered the blogosphere.  It&amp;rsquo;s been something I&amp;rsquo;ve been mulling over for a few years now, but something I never did commit to due to one excuse or another that I made up along the way.  I was content just &lt;em&gt;being&lt;/em&gt; &amp;hellip; or at least pretending like I was.  Content, that is.  One can&amp;rsquo;t help &amp;lsquo;being&amp;rsquo;.  It is a requirement of life, really.  Recently, though, this has changed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As one gets older one gains some realizations.  One of which is that our time is limited (for now).  This gets compounded when the people we love pass on.  &lt;em&gt;Especially&lt;/em&gt; when they are particularly close to us.  Priorities shift.  What was once less important becomes more.  What we could always just do later may just run out of that later.  But all of that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter to anyone but myself.  What matters is that I am now here and, more importantly, that &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; is now here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
